Personal Information

- Pie de Boer
- **4** 17 December 1996
- Q Dutch

Pie de Boer

Graduate - Data Science and Artificial Intelligence (BSc)

Enthusiastic and creative graduate from Maastricht University with a strong interest in machine learning, signal processing, and generative Al. I possess excellent interpersonal skills and a solid technical mindset, thriving in both collaborative **1** +31618928452 settings and individual research projects. In my spare time, I explore computer topics

> such as virtual machines, emulators, and Linux, delve into audio engineering, and engage in strength training.

Contact

- ★ 10715, Berlin
- □ piedeboer96@gmail.com
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/pie-deboer-6b6663265/
- nttp://github.com/piedeboer96

Competences

Programming Languages

(Advanced): Python, Java, MATLAB (Intermediate): C++, Clojure, R, SQL, Bash

Stack

Google Cloud, Git, Unix, PyTorch, TensorFlow, Jupyter Notebook, Scikit-Learn, Homebrew and more.

Group Projects

3D Bin Packing

Golf Simulator

Chess Engine

Multi Modal Assistant (Text, Speech and Vision)

Highlighted Courses

Machine Learning

Data Analysis

Probability and Statistics

Mathematical Modeling

Image & Video Processing

Quantum Computing

Robotics & Embedded Systems

Education

■ Data Science and Artificial Intelligence

Maastricht University, Maastricht | 2021 - 2024 Completed (180 ECTS)

Thesis: Conditional Diffusion Models for ECG Signal Denoising (8.5/10.0)

- ~ Trained using Google Cloud and PyTorch
- ~ Outperforming traditional signal processing methods found in MATLAB.

GPA: 8.28/10.0

Chemistry

Utrecht University, Utrecht | 2016 - 2017

Completed first year (60 ECTS) GPA: 7.48/10.0

■ VWO - Atheneum

Bonnefantencollege HAVO/VWO, Maastricht | 2009 - 2016

Profile: Nature & Technology and Nature & Health

Experience

Rabobank

Research Project | 2023 - 2024

Completed a six-month research project on a quantum approach to portfolio optimization. Utilized Python and the D-Wave API to interface with actual quantum hardware. Maintained weekly communication with a senior data scientist and closely collaborated with a researcher from TNO.

Self-Employed

Mathematics, Physics and Chemistry Tutor | 2019 - 2023

Tutored Dutch high school students in core science subjects from HAVO 3 to final exams, assisting up to seven students per week during peak times.

Additional Skills

- English (C1) German (B2) Dutch (Native)
- **MATLAB Fundamentals Certificate**